Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series VIII. Governmental Relations, 1961-1990; 8.76 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains correspondence, reports, budgets, and publications accumulated by the President's office from federal and state government departments and agencies which impacted NYU during the 1980s and early 1990s. Material dates from 1965 to 1990 and contains information on specific federal departments including the Department of Labor; Department of Defense; and Department of the Interior, as well as agencies including U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD); National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA); and the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA). Files in this series also contain information generated by the U.S. House of Representatives, the Senate, and New York State Senate and Assembly. Additionally, this series includes subject files containing reports and other publications on student loans, taxes, and drugs in schools.
  - Is it Deductable?, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Implementation of the Helsinki Accords, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Federal Tax and Budget Proposals, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Health and Human Services (HHS), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Interior, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Justice, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Labor, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - FY 1985 Federal Budget Impact on NYU (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Taxes on Faculty Housing and Related, 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Telephones, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Index of Documents for a Report, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Materials for a November 5th Meeting, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Wharton, Eggers Dialogue, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Humanities, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - NY State Congressional Delegation, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Letter to Mrs. Elmer H. Bobst, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - State -- Legislation, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Federal Departments and Agencies -- Department of Education, 1982-1985 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Pro-con Sheets, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Commerce, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Defense, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Energy, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Research and Development, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - FY 1985 Federal Budget Impact on NYU (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, City Government Correspondence, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Report, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Dinkins and Mark Green Correspondence, Clippings, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Dinkins Congratulations Letter, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Various Financial Issues, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 5-6)
  - Federal -- President of the U.S., 1983-1985 (Box 106, Folder 7-9)
  - Memo to Lynne Brown, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Reports on Federal Budget, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Memos, Reports on Federal Support for NYU and Student Loans, Clippings, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Memo on Conference on Drug Abuse, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Memos on Drug Issues, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Memos, Correspondence on Federal Education Guidelines, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - New York Mercantile Exchange Information Kit, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - K-12 Education, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Clippings, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Federal Department of Education, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Artifacts Indemnity Act Information Advisory, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Artifacts Indemnity Act, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - House Delegation Trip to the Soviet Union Report, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Reports on National Endowment for the Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Letters Against National Endowment for the Arts Funding Restrictions, H-Z, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Memos, Congressional Hearings Transcripts, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Memos on NYU in Albany Day, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence on National Endowment for the Arts Independent Commission, 1990-1990 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - New York State Budget Cuts, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
  - Memos, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence on State Budget, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Memos and Correspondence on State Budget, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with State Assembly, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Senate Calendar, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Memos, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Andrew Sanders Response to Frohnmayer Interview, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Russell Feingold, Memo, Clippings, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Memos, Clipping, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence on Eastern Europe, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Memos, Reports, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 12-13)
  - Correspondence with Mario Cuomo, Memo on State Budget Cuts, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Stan Lundine and Governor's Office, Memo on State Budget Cuts, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Federal -- House of Representatives, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - State -- Senate, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - State -- Assembly, 1983-1985 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Tax Legislation, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - State (New York), 1981-1985 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Percy Seitlin, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - "Special Education: A Call for Quality" Report, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Schedule, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Memos, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Members of Congress, Reports, 1961-1984; 1982-1984 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Retail Buying Book and Remarks, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Federal -- Senate, 1982-1985 (Box 111, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 1-7)
  - Correspondence, Memos on Federal Relations, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - State -- Office of the Governor, 1981-1985 (Box 113, Folder 1-3)
  - Federal Legislation, 1982-1985 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Tax Reform Conference Priorities of New York University, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - The Mayor's Management Report, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - City -- City Office of the Mayor, 1981-1985 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - City, 1980-1985 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Audit, 1982-1985 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Federal -- Departments and Agencies, 1983-1985 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 115, Folder 1-3)
  - Newsletters, Memos, Statements to Congress, 1983-1985 (Box 115, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence with Paul Simon, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Memos on Tax Laws, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - International Programs, Part II, 1983-1985 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - International Programs, Part I, 1984-1985 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Other States, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Government Relations Bulletin, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence with City Officials, Congressional Record, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Police Commissioner Benjamin Ward, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Office of the Mayor, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Quarterly Weekly Report, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - National Journal, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Federal Budget and Tax Laws, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 6-9)
  - Drugs on Campus, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Health and Human Services, USIA Report, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Federal Department of Education, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Memos, Transcripts, 1986-1986 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Report on Gramm-Rudman, FY 1987 Budget, and Tax Bill, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Letter from Jim Wright, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Memos on Senate Legislation, Letter to Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1986-1986 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Members of Congress, Memos on Rangel Meeting, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Senators, 1986-1987 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Federal Affairs -- Faculty Housing, 1984-1985 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Federal Affairs -- Science, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Federal Affairs -- Urban Institute, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Office of Governor Mario Cuomo, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Advisory Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Transcripts, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence with Elected Officials, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Legislative Summary, 1986-1986 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Warren G. Wilkinson, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Richard Thornburgh, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Federal Affairs -- Moynihan / Simon Bills, 1983-1985 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Reports on Federal Policies and Funding, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 1-5)
  - Correspondence with Senators and Congresspeople, Congressional Record, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - New York State Center for Neural Science at New York University, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - State Budget, Tuition Assistance Program, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Federal Affairs -- General, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Police Department, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - NYU and Public Schools, Police, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Briefing Book on FY1988 Budget Proposals (Box 121, Folder 3-6)
  - Institute of Museum Services, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Toward Civilization: A Report on Arts Education, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Americans and the Arts V, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Reports, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Federal Reports on Education, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - NIH Peer Review of Research Grant Applications, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Members of Congress, 1986-1988 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Senators, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Reports on New York State Education, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Mario Cuomo, Memos on State Funding, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Assistance Program, Memos, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Invitation Letters, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - New York City Partnership -- "Priorities for New York City", 1983 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - "Computers in Schools: The Federal Role", 1983 (Box 241, Folder 2)
- Series IX. Art and Memorabilia, 1975-1991; 3 Linear Feet in 1 flat box, 1 oversize box, and 1 flat-file folder.
  This series contains an artwork gifted to Brademas and his wife by the artist Chaim Gross; a collage art piece with storage case; and an academic gown hood worn by Brademas during ceremonies.
  - Limited Edition Print of NYU Motto and Torch, Presented to President Brademas, 1981; cuid17324 (Box 294)
  - 1975 Artwork -- "Children's Game" by Chaim Gross with 1986 Inscription to Brademas and His Wife, 1975, 1986; cuid17325 (Box Shared University Archives 046, Folder 7)
- Series X. Public Relations, 1975-1991; 22 Linear Feet in 47 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.; 33 VHS
  This series mainly contains public relations office material related to appearances and events Brademas attended or organized while serving as President of NYU. Files in this series contain requests for Brademas appearances and speeches; planning files for NYU events; and correspondence. A small collection of speeches in this series date from 1981 to 1984; however, a more comprehensive set can be found in Series XIII. Planning files for events hosted in Brademas' penthouse residence are in this series and typically include invitation lists, menus, and schedules. Clippings and press releases in this series feature Brademas and his connection to NYU. Photographic portraits of Brademas, as well as event photographs are in this series. Event photographs include parties at the Onassis Center in Greece, and Brademas' trips to Asia. A large number of video recordings in this series contain footage for a possible informational video for NYU's Villa La Pietra in Florence, Italy. These videos contain interviews with Sir Harold Acton, views of the building and grounds, and historical stock footage.
  - Correspondence, Memos, Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Local Community Groups, 1981-1982 (Box 143, Folder 2-4)
  - Community Board 2, 1981-1982 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Public Occasions and Commencement, 1980-1983 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1980-1982 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Invitations to Special Events, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Invited Speakers, Clippings on Veto, 1981-1983 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Freeze and Disarmament, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Kriser Presidential Lecture Series, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture Series, 1980-1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1979-1983 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Investiture -- Brademas, 1975-1981 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Publications -- University Press, 1980-1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Publications -- Non-University, 1981-1982 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Publications -- Acknowledgements, 1980-1983 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Condolences, 1980-1982 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - NYU Onassis Convocation - Brademas Interview in Greece, undated (Box 101, Video 34)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Speeches and Remarks, 1981-1983 (Box 145, Folder 6-8, Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Invitations and Thank You Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1980-1982 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Memos on Press Interviews, 1981-1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Thank You Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 146, Folder 5-9)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1982 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Public Occasions, 1982-1983 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 1982-1983 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Public Occasions -- Conferences, 1981-1982 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Public Occasions -- Convocations, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Sadat Convocation, 1981 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Public Occasions -- Receptions, Luncheons, Dinners, 1982-1983 (Box 147, Folder 6-7)
  - Dedications -- Public Occasions, 1980-1982 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Public Occasions -- Lectures, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Huntley Lectures, 1982-1983 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Kriser Presidential Seminar Series, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Salomon Lecture Series, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Publications -- Non-University, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Publications Request, 1980-1981 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Speeches and Remarks -- Requests for Participation, 1980-1982 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Condolences, 1982-1983 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Speech Drafts and Related Material, 1981-1984 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Speeches and Related Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 148, Folder 6-7)
  - Congratulations, 1981-1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Speech Schedules, Greek Orthodox Church, 1982-1983 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Visitors, 1982-1983 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Newspapers, 1983-1983 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Sponsorship -- Regretted Memberships, 1982-1983 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, 1982-1984 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Thanks -- Outgoing, 1982-1984 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1981-1983 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1982-1983 (Box 186, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Special Events, Penthouse, 1981-1984 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Penthouse Dinners, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - RSVPs: Douglas Davis Dinner, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - RSVPs: Mayor Koch Dinner, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - RSVPs: Congressional Brunch, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Liv Ullman, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Interviews, 1981-1983 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Long-Term Schedules, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report Letters, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Contributions Requested of Dr. Brademas, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Boards and Councils -- Requests to Participate, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Boards and Councils -- Declined Requests, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Memos on Press Coverage, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 3-7)
  - Penthouse Dinners, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1990 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and Press Release on Commencement, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Memos and Related Material on Public Occasions, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 2-6)
  - Commencement, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Marymount College Tarrytown Commencement Program, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - "P.L. 94-142: Ten Years Later" Conference, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 2-3)
  - Letter to Craig Morgan, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - C. Walter Nichols Award, Kean College Convocation, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Giulio Andreotti, Carlos Salinas Visits, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Patriarch Demetrios I Visit, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Invitations to Colin Powell and Elie Wiesel, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Declined Invitations, 1990 (Box 153, Folder 10-14)
  - Neighborhood Organizations, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Letter from Joe Dunbar, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Park Involvement, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Organizations and Local Residents, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - "Spruce Up 90" Event, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Park Complaint, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - NYU Community Fund Remarks, The Caring Community, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - The Caring Community, Complaint, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Local Residents, Traffic Issue, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Amnesty International, Campus Security, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Local Resident Concerns, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Memo to Lynne Brown, 1989 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Commencement, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Reports, Memos, Clippings, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 15-17)
  - Notre Dame Journal of Law, Ethics, and Public Policy, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Universities, Information Technologies, and Academic Libraries, 1981 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Third World Radical Regimes, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Arms Control Today, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Views in New York, 1980 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Humanities, 1985-1985 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - The New Deal: Fifty Years After, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Providing for the Needs of Black Students in the University, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Memo, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Publications, Press Releases, Memos, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 9-11, Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Speech Transcripts, 1984-1985 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Governors Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Other University Commencements, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Dental, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Memos and Invitations to Public Occasions, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Complaints and Responses RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Community Boards, The Public Agenda Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park Cleanup, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - PA Consulting, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - NYU Magazine Planning, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, 1984-1985 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Report, 1983-1985 (Box 158, Folder 1-3)
  - University Public Issues Committee, 1984 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Convocations, 1984-1985 (Box 158, Folder 6-8)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1985 (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
  - Graduate Education, 1983-1984 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Condolences, 1984-1985 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Notes, 1983-1985 (Box 159, Folder 5-6)
  - Press Releases, Press Office Packets, Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 160, Folder 1-4)
  - Press Releases, Memos, 1983-1985 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Fundraising Request, 1983-1985 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Duke of Alba, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Kriser Professorship in Anthropology, 1985 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Iakovos, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1984-1985 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, Newsletters, Lectures, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Letter from Police Assistant Chief, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Community Relations, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Drug Efforts, 1985-1986 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Notice about LaGuardia Statue, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Community Board 2, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Concerns, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Complaints RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Memo on Photograph, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Commencement, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Governors Conference, Virginia Commonwealth University Commencement, 1985-1987 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Convocations, 1987-1987 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Corazon Aquino Event Thank Yous, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Founder's Day Convocation, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Awards, Special Events, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 6-7)
  - Muskie Lecture, 1986 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Special Event Planning, 1984-1986 (Box 162, Folder 9-11)
  - Hoosiers, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Colloquiums and Lectures, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Symposiums and Lectures, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 4-5)
  - Invitation to Saul Bellow, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Petrie Lecture, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Weekend Conference, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Centennial Convocation, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Report, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Basketball, School of Continuing Education Pamphlets, Mario Cuomo Address, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, Correspondence, Press Contact List, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, Memos, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Magazines, Newsletters, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
  - Reports, Clippings, Memos, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 3-5)
  - Memos and Correspondence on New York University Magazine, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Memos, Correspondence and Drafts for New York University Magazine, 1986 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Condolences, 1986-1987 (Box 164, Folder 8-9)
  - Congratulatory Letter, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Thank You Letter, 1988 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Jessup Interview re: Nancy Hanks, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Interviews, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 3-5)
  - Memo on Trustee Escorts, 1988 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Dinners, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 7-9)
  - Interviews, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
  - The Atlantic Council, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Penthouse Dinner, 1984 (Box 166, Folder 4)